Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
Have you heard
هل سمعت؟
the latest rumor in town?
ما هي الشائعة الأخيرة في المدينة؟
What rumor?
ما هي الشائعة؟
A storyteller has a little ghost.
لدى راوي القصص شبح صغير.
His words can kill people.
كلماته قد تقتل الناس.
Absorbing corpses and poisons,
امتصاص الجثث والسموم،
the little ghost took human form.
الشبح الصغير اتخذ شكلًا بشريًا.
It's really weird.
إنه أمر غريب حقا.
Who is this storyteller?
من هو هذا الراوي؟
Fang Zhiyuan of Inviting Moon House.
فانغ تشي يوان من دعوة منزل القمر.
[Treasure at Dawn] ♪Reach the highest level♪
[كنز عند الفجر] ♪الوصول إلى أعلى مستوى♪
♪Reach the state of no desire, illuminate the virtuous light♪
♪الوصول إلى حالة عدم الرغبة، وإضاءة النور الفاضل♪
♪Man is upright because he is moral, and he is strong because he is upright♪
♪الإنسان مستقيم لأنه أخلاقي، وهو قوي لأنه مستقيم♪
♪Upright, strong, and fair♪
♪ مستقيم، قوي، وعادل♪
♪I am the fire♪
♪أنا النار♪
♪Burning out all desires♪
♪حرق كل الرغبات♪
♪River can't put me out♪
♪النهر لا يستطيع إخراجي♪
♪Yang's beginning leads to development. Wu Chi creates Tai Chi♪
♪بداية يانغ تُفضي إلى التطور. وو تشي يُبدع تاي تشي♪
♪People mistake their bodily form, forgetting the true mind within♪
♪يخطئ الناس في فهم شكل أجسادهم، وينسون العقل الحقيقي في داخلهم♪
♪People make their own enemies♪
♪الناس يصنعون أعداءهم♪
♪Books are all about reason. People are full of purpose♪
الكتب كلها تدور حول المنطق. الناس مليئون بالهدف.
♪People are overrun by illusions♪
♪الناس غارقون في الأوهام♪
♪They are fascinated by illusions♪
♪إنهم مفتونون بالأوهام♪
♪With a pure mind, sitting in the clouds♪
♪مع عقل نقي، جالسًا في السحاب♪
♪Watching people creating dreams♪
♪مشاهدة الناس وهم يصنعون الأحلام♪
♪Is it painful to live in the world?♪
♪هل العيش في العالم مؤلم؟♪
♪Learn from nature. Forget all your desires♪
♪تعلم من الطبيعة. انسَ كل رغباتك♪
♪How about clearing all my thoughts?♪
♪ماذا عن تصفية كل أفكاري؟♪
♪Moths fly into the fire♪
♪العث يطير في النار♪
♪The fire melts old shackles♪
♪النار تذيب القيود القديمة♪
♪Today, I know it's me♪
♪اليوم، أعلم أنه أنا♪
[Treasure at Dawn]
[كنز عند الفجر]
[Episode 15] [Greed Kills Hua Lei, Night Owl Strikes Again]
[الحلقة 15] [الجشع يقتل هوا لي، بومة الليل تضرب مرة أخرى]
Like it?
هل يعجبك ذلك؟
Why did you come back?
لماذا عدت؟
Why can't I come back?
لماذا لا أستطيع العودة؟
Now, is this a home
الآن، هل هذا هو المنزل؟
for you and my brother?
لك ولأخي؟
What are you talking about?
ماذا تتحدث عنه؟
Wasn't it you who got these for us?
ألم تكن أنت الذي حصلت على هذه الأشياء لنا؟
You haven't eaten, have you?
لم تأكل، أليس كذلك؟
I'll see what else
سأرى ماذا ايضا
is on the stove to eat.
على الموقد لتناول الطعام.
Jibei Chamber of Commerce's seal.
ختم غرفة تجارة جيبي.
I underestimated you.
لقد قللت من شأنك.
Did you get it by betraying me?
هل حصلت عليه عن طريق خيانتي؟
What are you talking about?
ماذا تتحدث عنه؟
These are the dowries given to me by the Chamber of Commerce.
هذه هي المهور التي أعطتها لي غرفة التجارة.
By the way, where's your brother?
بالمناسبة، أين أخوك؟
Why isn't he back yet?
لماذا لم يعود بعد؟
He won't be back tonight.
لن يعود الليلة.
I asked someone to take him to a big dinner.
طلبت من أحد الأشخاص أن يأخذه إلى حفل عشاء كبير.
If you like money, tell me.
إذا كنت تحب المال أخبرني.
I can fulfill your wish.
أستطيع تحقيق رغبتك.
Come on.
تعال.
Sit down.
اجلس.
It's a long night. We have plenty of time.
إنها ليلة طويلة، لدينا متسع من الوقت.
Yes. We're tired after all this talk.
نعم، لقد تعبنا بعد كل هذا الحديث.
Let's sit down and talk.
دعونا نجلس ونتحدث.
Siming.
سيمينغ.
Don't think I'm with Chairman Li
لا أعتقد أنني مع الرئيس لي
just because I used to be
فقط لأنني كنت كذلك
with the Chamber of Commerce.
مع غرفة التجارة.
I've been in your family
لقد كنت في عائلتك
since I married your brother.
منذ أن تزوجت أخاك.
In fact,
في الحقيقة،
I always thought
لقد اعتقدت دائما
the man I married was you,
الرجل الذي تزوجته كان أنت
but I didn't realize
ولكنني لم أدرك ذلك
it was your brother.
لقد كان أخاك.
It's a cruel fate,
إنه مصير قاسي
but actually,
ولكن في الواقع،
the person I love
الشخص الذي أحبه
has always been you, Siming.
لقد كنت دائما أنت، سيمينغ.
Can't you
ألا يمكنك؟
look at me?
انظر إليَّ؟
Mr. Sun.
السيد صن.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Entertaining.
مسلية.
Mr. Sun, are you hungry?
سيد الشمس هل أنت جائع؟
Yes. I'm going home for dinner.
نعم سأذهب إلى المنزل لتناول العشاء.
Sir, don't go home.
سيدي لا تذهب إلى المنزل.
How about we take you
ماذا عن أن نأخذك؟
to the best restaurant in town?
إلى أفضل مطعم في المدينة؟
Really?
حقًا؟
Yes.
نعم.
OK. That's what you said.
حسنًا، هذا ما قلته.
I...
أنا...
I love you, too,
أحبك أيضًا،
because I'm the same person as you
لأنني نفس الشخص مثلك
who won't miss any opportunity
من لن يفوت أي فرصة
to step on someone else's head to get ahead.
أن تدوس على رأس شخص آخر لتتقدم.
You like gold, don't you?
أنت تحب الذهب، أليس كذلك؟
There's plenty of it in the other world.
هناك الكثير منه في العالم الآخر.
I'll offer you as much as you want.
سأقدم لك ما تريد.
Only stupid men die
فقط الرجال الأغبياء يموتون
because of women.
بسبب النساء.
Do you think I'm that kind of man?
هل تعتقد أنني هذا النوع من الرجال؟
Do you think I'm that kind of person?
هل تعتقد أنني هذا النوع من الأشخاص؟
Do you think I'm human?
هل تعتقد أنني إنسان؟
[Like the Rising Sun]
[مثل شروق الشمس]
Chairman.
رئيس مجلس الإدارة.
Ma Gang's lieutenant
ملازم عصابتي
Xubu Huai is dead.
لقد مات شوبو هواي.
Dead?
ميت؟
Good.
جيد.
He died in front of the Chamber of Commerce.
توفي أمام غرفة التجارة.
What?
ماذا؟
Emergency. Let's go.
حالة طوارئ. هيا بنا.
So what are we eating?
إذن ماذا نأكل؟
Where are you guys?
أين أنتم يا شباب؟
Shouldn't we...
ألا ينبغي لنا...
Honey, give me the horse.
عزيزتي أعطيني الحصان.
I'm going to Siming.
سأذهب إلى سيمينغ.
Honey.
عسل.
Siming, you are here?
سيمينغ، أنت هنا؟
Then I won't go to you.
إذن لن أذهب إليك.
By the way,
بالمناسبة،
Ma Gang's Xubu Huai is dead.
لقد مات Xubu Huai من Ma Gang.
Right in front of the Chamber of Commerce.
مباشرة أمام غرفة التجارة.
I thought
اعتقدت
it was something you had to know,
لقد كان شيئًا يجب عليك معرفته،
so I came back to you.
لذلك عدت إليك.
My brother.
أخي.
If I were to give you a new bride every day,
لو أعطيتك عروسة جديدة كل يوم،
would you agree?
هل توافق؟
That's not appropriate.
هذا ليس مناسبا.
You know your sister-in-law.
أنت تعرف أخت زوجتك.
Go in and take a look.
ادخل وألقي نظرة.
She may not object.
لا يجوز لها الاعتراض.
Siming.
سيمينغ.
Say what you want to say.
قل ما تريد قوله.
How many wives can I buy with this?
كم زوجة أستطيع أن أشتري بهذا؟
Don't you want to ask something else?
ألا تريد أن تسأل شيئا آخر؟
Anything my brother has done is right.
كل ما فعله أخي هو الصواب.
Look.
ينظر.
Our mom was right.
كانت أمنا على حق.
Pretty women are mistresses.
النساء الجميلات هن عشيقات.
Yes.
نعم.
Because our father had a mistress,
لأن والدنا كان له عشيقة،
our mom killed her and was executed.
أمنا قتلتها وأعدمت.
That's why we're orphans.
لهذا السبب نحن أيتام.
Stop crying.
توقف عن البكاء.
Let's go
دعنا نذهب
and watch the fun.
وشاهد المرح.
Siming. Siming.
سيمينغ. سيمينغ.
So am I still buying a wife?
فهل مازلت أشتري زوجة؟
Of course.
بالطبع.
I'll buy you a fat woman this time.
سأشتري لك امرأة سمينة هذه المرة.
Will a fat woman be expensive?
هل المرأة السمينة ستكون غالية الثمن؟
That's what we want.
هذا ما نريده.
No.
لا.
Actually, I think a woman like your sister-in-law is quite nice.
في الواقع، أعتقد أن امرأة مثل أخت زوجك لطيفة جدًا.
Gentlemen, I've done the autopsy.
أيها السادة، لقد قمت بالتشريح.
How did he die?
كيف مات؟
There was a stab wound on the body,
كان هناك طعنة في الجسم.
but there was no blood
ولكن لم يكن هناك دم
and scorched ash
والرماد المحروق
inside the wound,
داخل الجرح،
so this was caused after his death, which is consistent
لذا فقد حدث هذا بعد وفاته، وهو أمر متسق
with what the Chamber of Commerce fighter who found the deceased said.
مع ما قاله مقاتل غرفة التجارة الذي عثر على الجثة.
The autopsy results show
وتظهر نتائج التشريح
that his real cause of death
أن السبب الحقيقي لوفاته
was a lightning strike.
كانت ضربة البرق.
Nonsense.
هراء.
How could it be so coincidental
كيف يمكن أن يكون هذا مصادفة؟
that he was struck by lightning while walking past here?
أنه أصيب بصاعقة أثناء مروره من هنا؟
Are you lying to me together with this post-mortem examiner?
هل تكذب عليّ مع هذا الطبيب الشرعي؟
Che.
الذي - التي.
There is a lot of doubt,
هناك الكثير من الشك،
and you haven't explained to us
ولم تشرح لنا
why Xubu Huai came to the gate.
لماذا جاء Xubu Huai إلى البوابة.
Isn't it a bit arbitrary
أليس هذا تعسفيا بعض الشيء
to put the blame on us?
لوضع اللوم علينا؟
My man died at your gate.
لقد مات رجلي عند بابك.
If you don't give me
إذا لم تعطيني
an explanation about this,
توضيح حول هذا الموضوع
I won't let you go.
لن أدعك تذهب.
In my opinion, there's nothing unusual.
في رأيي، لا يوجد شيء غير عادي.
How can a son come
كيف يأتي الابن
to his father's territory and act wild?
إلى أراضي والده ويتصرف بوحشية؟
It's reasonable for such an unfilial son
من المعقول أن يكون مثل هذا الابن غير الأبوي
to be struck by lightning.
أن تضربها الصاعقة.
Do you want to die?
هل تريد أن تموت؟
Are you angry?
هل أنت غاضب؟
Che.
الذي - التي.
I've respected you enough.
لقد احترمتك بما فيه الكفاية.
This is the Jibei Chamber of Commerce.
هذه هي غرفة تجارة جيبي.
After today, it's hard to say.
بعد اليوم، من الصعب أن أقول.
Guys.
شباب.
Yes, sir.
نعم سيدي.
Get ready.
استعد.
Stop it.
اوقفها.
Please calm down.
من فضلك اهدأ.
You don't have to get physical.
لا يتوجب عليك أن تكون جسديًا.
Lord Wen.
اللورد وين.
The post-mortem examiner has completed the autopsy.
لقد أكمل الطبيب الشرعي عملية تشريح الجثة.
Xubu Huai was killed by lightning,
قُتل شوبو هواي بسبب البرق،
but Che is being unreasonable.
لكن تشي غير معقول.
Lord Wen.
اللورد وين.
This time, Ma Gang's dead.
هذه المرة، ما جانج مات.
You can't send us away
لا يمكنك أن ترسلنا بعيدا
just by talking.
فقط بالتحدث.
Without an explanation
بدون تفسير
about this incident today,
حول هذا الحادث اليوم،
my knife is going to be stained with blood.
سكينتي سوف تكون ملطخة بالدماء.
So what explanation do you want?
إذن ما هو التفسير الذي تريده؟
Xubu Huai is dead,
لقد مات شوبو هواي
but his family has to live.
لكن يجب على عائلته أن تعيش.
How about this?
ماذا عن هذا؟
The Chamber of Commerce gives us a 30% profit.
غرفة التجارة تعطينا ربحًا بنسبة 30٪.
I'll send the rest
سأرسل الباقي
to Xubu Huai's mother.
إلى والدة Xubu Huai.
30%?
30%؟
Maybe it's better to just rob.
ربما يكون من الأفضل أن تسرق فقط.
Good idea.
فكرة جيدة.
Mr. Che.
السيد تشي.
I will have this case investigated thoroughly,
سأقوم بالتحقيق في هذه القضية بشكل شامل،
and you will get results,
وسوف تحصل على النتائج
but if you
ولكن إذا كنت
use the death of your man as an excuse
استخدمي موت زوجك كذريعة
to enrich yourself,
لإثراء نفسك،
your other men will be disappointed, won't they?
سوف يشعر رجالك الآخرون بخيبة الأمل، أليس كذلك؟
Tuoba Ruo.
توبا رو.
Yes.
نعم.
She never worries me.
إنها لا تقلقني أبدًا.
Good.
جيد.
Che.
الذي - التي.
Good luck in finding the culprit.
أتمنى لك حظا سعيدا في العثور على الجاني.
Don't mess it up.
لا تفسد الأمر.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Leave the body here.
اترك الجثة هنا.
No one can touch him until the investigation is over.
لا يمكن لأحد أن يمسه حتى ينتهي التحقيق.
Bring in anyone
احضر أي شخص
who saw Xubu Huai
من رأى شوبو هواي
in the 24 hours before he died.
في الـ 24 ساعة التي سبقت وفاته.
Kill those
اقتل هؤلاء
who don't follow,
الذين لا يتبعون
those
أولئك
who resist,
الذين يقاومون
and those
وهؤلاء
who try to escape!
الذين يحاولون الهروب!
Yes!
نعم!
[Vivid Stories]
[قصص حية]
The night is dark, and the waves are heavy.
الليل مظلم والأمواج ثقيلة.
Bandits are rampant in Xichuan.
قطاع الطرق منتشرون في شيتشوان.
It is only natural that the rebellion be put down.
ومن الطبيعي أن يتم قمع التمرد.
No villain
لا يوجد شرير
lives long.
يعيش طويلا.
- Nice. - Nice.
- لطيف. - لطيف.
Today, our story is
اليوم قصتنا هي
of the Jibei Chamber of Commerce's own hero,
من بطل غرفة تجارة جيبي،
Hua Lei.
هوا لي.
Hello, Mr. Hua.
مرحباً، السيد المنتج.
Mr. Hua.
السيد المنتج.
Did my mother give me any messages?
هل أعطتني أمي أي رسائل؟
No.
لا.
Mr. Hua.
السيد المنتج.
Has my mother been to a physician about her eyes?
هل ذهبت والدتي إلى الطبيب بشأن عينيها؟
What did the physician say?
ماذا قال الطبيب؟
Is her eye disease curable?
هل مرض عينيها قابل للشفاء؟
What?
ماذا؟
Am I your servant?
هل أنا خادمك؟
Should you ask me about that?
هل يجب عليك أن تسألني عن ذلك؟
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
Fang Zhiyuan.
فانغ تشي يوان.
[Vivid Stories]
[قصص حية]
Are you a storyteller
هل أنت راوي قصص؟
or a doomsayer?
أو من المتنبئين بالهلاك؟
Yesterday, you finished the story of Xubu Huai,
لقد انتهيت أمس من قصة Xubu Huai،
and he died.
ومات.
You are now talking about Hua Lei,
أنت تتحدث الآن عن هوا لي،
so will he die too?
فهل سيموت هو أيضا؟
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- نعم نعم.
Are you a prophet of disaster?
هل أنت نبي الكوارث؟
Speaking of Hua Lei,
وفي حديثه عن هوا لي،
he was a fierce fighter
لقد كان مقاتلا شرسا
and especially good at catching thieves.
وخاصة أنها جيدة في القبض على اللصوص.
Thieves in Xichuan
لصوص في شيتشوان
who are on the wanted list
من هم على قائمة المطلوبين
tremble in fear
ارتجف من الخوف
when they hear his name.
عندما يسمعون اسمه.
That audience member asked me
سألني ذلك العضو من الجمهور
why Hua Lei
لماذا هوا لي
likes catching thieves so much.
يحب اصطياد اللصوص كثيراً.
That's interesting.
هذا ممتع.
Hua Lei is not interested
هوا لي غير مهتم
in power or official positions.
في السلطة أو المناصب الرسمية.
He only
هو فقط
likes money.
يحب المال.
I was so anxious to learn that my mother
كنت متشوقة جدًا لمعرفة أن والدتي
had suddenly contracted an eye disease
أصيب فجأة بمرض في العين
and lost her sight, but there was nothing I could do.
وفقدت بصرها، ولكن لم يكن هناك شيء أستطيع أن أفعله.
Fortunately, you helped me
لحسن الحظ أنك ساعدتني
and brought the money to my mother
وأحضرت المال إلى والدتي
to hire a physician for her,
لتعيين طبيب لها،
but I missed my mother
ولكنني افتقدت والدتي
without any news about her,
دون أي أخبار عنها،
so I just...
لذلك أنا فقط...
Sir.
سيد.
Get lost.
اغرب عن وجهي.
Mr. Hua, you're so powerful.
السيد هوا، أنت قوي جدًا.
When you came to use my horses,
عندما أتيت لاستخدام خيولي،
you not only didn't inform me
لم تخبرني فقط
but also played bully to my subordinates.
ولكنني لعبت أيضًا دور المتسلط على مرؤوسي.
It seems you don't care
يبدو أنك لا تهتم
about me,
ْعَنِّي،
the new carriage steward.
موظف النقل الجديد.
I did the same thing
لقد فعلت نفس الشيء
when Feng was here.
عندما كان فينج هنا.
That's why Feng is useless
لهذا السبب فنغ عديم الفائدة
and Chairman Li looks down on him.
وينظر إليه الرئيس لي بازدراء.
That makes me what I am today.
وهذا ما يجعلني ما أنا عليه اليوم.
Do you want Chairman Li
هل تريد الرئيس لي
to look down on me too?
لتنظر إليّ أيضًا؟
What do you want?
ماذا تريد؟
You.
أنت.
Clean the stables
تنظيف الاسطبلات
with Mr. Hua,
مع السيد هوا،
or he doesn't know how to respect people.
أو أنه لا يعرف كيف يحترم الناس.
Sun Siming.
صن سيمينج.
Don't go too far.
لا تذهب بعيدا جدا.
Too far?
هل هو بعيد جداً؟
Who is going too far?
من يذهب بعيدا جدا؟
OK.
نعم.
Let's go to Chairman Li
دعونا نذهب إلى الرئيس لي
and ask him to comment on this.
واطلب منه التعليق على هذا.
Steward Sun.
ستيوارد صن.
I was offensive.
لقد كنت مسيئا.
I'll clean the stables later.
سأقوم بتنظيف الإسطبلات لاحقًا.
Mr. Chairman
السيد الرئيس
doesn't need to know about this.
لا داعي لمعرفة هذا.
You're smart.
أنت ذكي.
Do a good job.
قم بعمل جيد.
Give him a broom.
أعطيه مكنسة.
Idiot.
غبي.
Mr. Hua.
السيد المنتج.
This...
هذا...
Brat, even you dare to humiliate me.
يا ولدي، حتى أنت تجرؤ على إذلالي.
I'll tell you the truth.
سأخبرك الحقيقة.
Your money has been
لقد تم تحويل أموالك
in my pocket for a long time.
في جيبي لفترة طويلة.
Do you still need to ask me?
هل لا تزال بحاجة إلى أن تسألني؟
Do you?
هل أنت؟
[Vivid Stories] That night, it was a dark night.
[قصص حية] تلك الليلة كانت ليلة مظلمة.
Hua Lei came to the headquarters of the Jibei Chamber of Commerce.
جاء هوا لي إلى مقر غرفة تجارة جيبي.
In one night,
في ليلة واحدة،
he arrested five thieves.
ألقى القبض على خمسة لصوص.
Only Night Owl,
فقط بومة الليل،
who had the highest bounty on the most wanted list,
من كان لديه أعلى مكافأة في قائمة المطلوبين،
was left scurrying away.
لقد ترك مسرعا بعيدا.
He's here.
إنه هنا.
Please forgive me.
رجائاً أعطني.
Where were you last night?
أين كنت الليلة الماضية؟
I was waiting
كنت أنتظر
outside the tavern
خارج الحانة
for my master last night,
لسيدي الليلة الماضية،
and then I suddenly had the call of nature,
ثم فجأة شعرت بحاجة إلى الذهاب إلى الطبيعة،
so I went to a remote location
لذلك ذهبت إلى مكان بعيد
to urinate,
للتبول
but I was knocked unconscious
لكنني فقدت الوعي
and didn't wake up until this morning.
ولم أستيقظ حتى هذا الصباح.
Is there anyone to testify for you?
هل هناك من يشهد لك؟
Please spare me.
أرجوك أن تنقذني.
Please, ma'am, spare me.
من فضلك سيدتي، أنقذيني.
Spare me.
انقذني.
If you hadn't gone AWOL,
لو لم تكن قد ذهبت AWOL،
how could Xubu Huai have died?
كيف يمكن أن يموت Xubu Huai؟
Your family will be taken care of later.
سيتم الاهتمام بعائلتك لاحقًا.
Go to hell in peace.
اذهب إلى الجحيم بسلام.
It's not my fault.
إنه ليس خطئي.
Please.
لو سمحت.
Spare me, please.
أرجوك أنقذني.
He didn't deserve to die, did he?
لم يستحق الموت، أليس كذلك؟
There are laws in Xichuan.
هناك قوانين في شيتشوان.
The Ma Gang is so powerful
عصابة ما قوية جدًا
that you can kill at will.
أنك تستطيع أن تقتل متى شئت.
What are you doing here?
ما الذي تفعله هنا؟
The crime this man committed
الجريمة التي ارتكبها هذا الرجل
is not enough for him to die here.
ليس كافيا له أن يموت هنا.
Don't interfere with my investigation.
لا تتدخل في تحقيقاتي.
Take him away.
خذه بعيدا.
Wait a minute.
انتظر دقيقة.
Song Jingye's death was investigated by us.
لقد قمنا بالتحقيق في وفاة سونغ جينغي.
If my friend is kind enough to help you,
إذا كان صديقي لطيفًا بما يكفي لمساعدتك،
why do you refuse?
لماذا ترفض؟
Ma Gang's business
أعمال ما جانج
will be handled by ourselves.
سيتم التعامل مع هذا الأمر بأنفسنا.
We don't bother outsiders.
نحن لا نزعج الغرباء.
If you guys don't leave,
إذا لم تغادروا يا رفاق،
don't blame me for being rude.
لا تلومني على كوني وقحًا.
He ran towards the backstage.
ركض نحو الكواليس.
Let's not argue anymore.
دعونا لا نتجادل بعد الآن.
Catch him first.
قبض عليه أولا.
This guy seems to have some skills.
يبدو أن هذا الرجل لديه بعض المهارات.
Maybe he can help.
ربما يمكنه المساعدة.
Whoever the murderer is
من هو القاتل
in this case,
في هذه الحالة،
it's bound to cause a big mess.
ومن المؤكد أنه سيسبب فوضى كبيرة.
It's better if we don't get him involved.
من الأفضل أن لا نجعله متورطًا.
This nerd does have some skills.
هذا المهووس لديه بعض المهارات.
At least,
على الأقل،
he can save many lives.
بإمكانه إنقاذ العديد من الأرواح.
Young Mistress.
سيدة شابة.
Come tomorrow if you want to hear a story.
تعالوا غدًا إذا كنتم تريدون سماع قصة.
I'm not performing today.
لن أؤدي اليوم.
We didn't come to hear a story
لم نأتِ لسماع قصة
but to see you.
ولكن لرؤيتك.
How can I be of service, Young Mistress?
كيف يمكنني أن أكون في خدمتك، سيدتي الشابة؟
We want to know
نريد أن نعرف
if you have a little ghost.
إذا كان لديك شبح صغير.
Sir, are you telling jokes?
سيدي هل أنت تمزح؟
I make money by telling stories.
أكسب المال عن طريق سرد القصص.
I earn just enough to support myself.
أنا أكسب ما يكفي لدعم نفسي.
By now,
بحلول الآن،
I can't even afford a woman,
لا أستطيع حتى تحمل تكلفة امرأة،
let alone a little ghost.
ناهيك عن شبح صغير.
But l heard
ولكنني سمعت
you're worth a lot of money.
أنت تستحق الكثير من المال.
Who told you that?
من قال لك ذلك؟
Look.
ينظر.
All my assets are here.
جميع أصولي موجودة هنا.
If it weren't for Inviting Moon House's proprietor taking me in,
إذا لم يكن الأمر يتعلق بدعوة صاحب منزل القمر لاستقبالي،
I'm afraid I'd have been living on the streets.
أخشى أن أعيش في الشوارع.
I heard you
لقد سمعتك
ransomed a piece of jade for five gold
فدى قطعة من اليشم مقابل خمسة ذهب
at the Fuquan Pawn Shop
في محل فوكوان للرهن
some time ago.
منذ بعض الوقت.
What?
ماذا؟
What shop?
أي متجر؟
I've never been there.
لم أكن هناك أبدًا.
I won't make five gold
لن أحصل على خمسة ذهب
even if I make money from storytelling for my whole life.
حتى لو كنت أكسب المال من رواية القصص طوال حياتي.
[Owner: Fang Zhiyuan. Holder: Fuquan Pawn Shop]
[المالك: فانغ تشي يوان. المالك: متجر فوكوان للرهونات]
That is indeed
هذا هو بالفعل
my name,
اسمي
but there may be someone else
ولكن قد يكون هناك شخص آخر
in such a big city who shares the same name with me.
في مدينة كبيرة مثل هذه التي تشترك معي في نفس الاسم.
Unfortunately, he and I share the same name but different destinies.
لسوء الحظ، أنا وهو نتقاسم نفس الاسم ولكن مصيرنا مختلف.
His destiny is so good
مصيره جيد جدا
that he has five gold to buy jade
أنه لديه خمسة ذهب لشراء اليشم
while I don't even have fifty coins,
في حين أنني لا أملك حتى خمسين قطعة نقدية،
right?
يمين؟
So it's not you?
إذن أنت لست أنت؟
Of course not.
بالطبع لا.
I know
أنا أعرف
there's been a rumor here recently
لقد كانت هناك شائعة هنا مؤخرًا
that my performance
أن أدائي
caused Xubu Huai to lose his life.
تسبب في وفاة Xubu Huai.
But
لكن
how is that possible?
كيف ذلك ممكنا؟
If a story can kill people,
إذا كانت القصة قادرة على قتل الناس،
why don't I talk
لماذا لا اتحدث
about the outlaws
عن الخارجين عن القانون
on the wanted list?
في قائمة المطلوبين؟
I can both kill those bandits
أنا قادر على قتل هؤلاء اللصوص
and get the bounty,
واحصل على المكافأة
which is enough for me to live for the rest of my life.
وهو ما يكفيني للعيش بقية حياتي.
That makes sense.
هذا منطقي.
I'd do it
سأفعل ذلك
if I could.
إذا أستطعت.
So we've got the wrong guy.
إذن لقد حصلنا على الرجل الخطأ.
Sorry to interrupt.
عذرا على المقاطعة.
Young Mistress, see you later.
سيدتي الشابة، أراك لاحقًا.
See you later.
أراك لاحقًا.
[Inviting Moon House]
[دعوة بيت القمر]
See you, Young Mistress.
أراك لاحقا يا سيدتي الشابة.
Maybe it really wasn't him?
ربما لم يكن هو حقا؟
How can a storyteller
كيف يمكن لراوي القصص
have so much money?
هل لديك الكثير من المال؟
[Fang Zhiyuan Talks About Heroes]
[فانغ تشي يوان يتحدث عن الأبطال]
Waiter.
النادل.
Who wrote this plaque?
من كتب هذه اللوحة؟
Mr. Fang, of course.
السيد فانغ، بالطبع.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
[Fang Zhiyuan Talks About Heroes Owner: Fang Zhiyuan]
[فانغ تشي يوان يتحدث عن مالك الأبطال: فانغ تشي يوان]
There are no two Fang Zhiyuan.
لا يوجد اثنان فانغ تشي يوان.
[Fang]
[ناب]
There's definitely something wrong
هناك بالتأكيد شيء خاطئ
with Fang Zhiyuan.
مع فانغ تشي يوان.
There are only two roughnecks here, my brother and I.
لا يوجد هنا سوى اثنين من العمال القاسيين، أنا وأخي.
Please bear with my lack of hospitality.
من فضلك تحمل افتقاري للضيافة.
Where is Madam?
أين سيدتي؟
She fell ill,
لقد مرضت
very ill,
مريض جدا
and died in the night.
ومات في الليل.
According to the rules of our hometown,
وفقا لقواعد مدينتنا،
we cremated her
لقد أحرقناها
and scattered her ashes in the forest
ونثرت رمادها في الغابة
to return her to nature.
لإعادتها إلى طبيعتها.
Aren't you a bit hasty?
ألا أنت متسرع بعض الشيء؟
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
My condolences.
تعازيّ.
Why did my two benefactors
لماذا قام اثنان من المحسنين
come here so late at night?
هل تأتي إلى هنا في وقت متأخر من الليل؟
What do you think
ماذا تعتقد
of Xubu Huai's death?
من وفاة Xubu Huai؟
It's a good thing.
إنه شيء جيد.
Have you heard the rumor
هل سمعت الشائعة؟
in the streets?
في الشوارع؟
The ballad?
القصيدة ؟
A storyteller
راوي القصص
has a little ghost.
لديه شبح صغير.
His words can kill people.
كلماته قد تقتل الناس.
Absorbing corpses and poisons,
امتصاص الجثث والسموم،
the little ghost took human form.
الشبح الصغير اتخذ شكلًا بشريًا.
That's right. That's it.
هذا صحيح. هذا كل شيء.
How can there be ghosts in the world?
كيف يمكن أن يكون هناك أشباح في العالم؟
I asked the two men
سألت الرجلين
who were guarding the main gate that night.
الذين كانوا يحرسون البوابة الرئيسية تلك الليلة.
They said they saw
قالوا أنهم رأوا
with their own eyes
بأعينهم
that lightning started the fire.
هذا البرق هو الذي بدأ الحريق.
Does this look man-made?
هل يبدو هذا من صنع الإنسان؟
Maybe
ربما
Xubu Huai was really killed
لقد قُتل شوبو هواي بالفعل
by a ghost.
بواسطة شبح.
You're new to Xichuan,
أنت جديد في شيتشوان،
so you don't know Xubu Huai.
لذلك أنت لا تعرف Xubu Huai.
This man is vicious and cruel.
هذا الرجل شرير وقاسي.
Countless people have died at his hands.
لقد مات عدد لا يحصى من الناس على يديه.
If the storyteller really did this,
لو كان الراوي قد فعل هذا حقا،
I think it's a good thing
أعتقد أنه شيء جيد
because he's done people a favor.
لأنه قدم خدمة للناس.
But it was a human life.
ولكنها كانت حياة انسانية.
Mr. Fu's benevolence is admirable,
إن إحسان السيد فو أمر مثير للإعجاب،
but your understanding of the matter
لكن فهمك للموضوع
may be a little pedantic.
ربما يكون متشددًا بعض الشيء.
I'm a straight talker.
أنا أتحدث بصراحة.
Sorry to offend you.
آسف لإهانتك.
Anyway, it's done,
على أية حال، لقد تم ذلك.
and he's dead,
وهو ميت
so you can't do anything about it,
لذلك لا يمكنك فعل أي شيء حيال ذلك،
no matter how amazing you are, right?
بغض النظر عن مدى روعتك، أليس كذلك؟
He's completely dead.
لقد مات تماما.
We couldn't save him,
لم نتمكن من انقاذه
but you know
لكنك تعلم
my friend
صديقي
is obsessed with medicine.
مهووس بالطب.
Xubu Huai's death from a thunderbolt is rare,
إن موت شوبو هواي بسبب الصاعقة أمر نادر الحدوث،
so my friend
لذلك صديقي
became curious
أصبح فضوليًا
and wanted
وأراد
to find out.
لمعرفة ذلك.
So you guys
لذا يا رفاق
want my help?
هل تريد مساعدتي؟
I hope you say yes.
أتمنى أن تقول نعم.
No problem,
لا مشكلة،
but I have one condition.
ولكن لدي شرط واحد.
Go ahead.
تفضل.
Whatever you find out,
مهما وجدت،
I have to be the first to know.
يجب أن أكون أول من يعرف.
Fine.
بخير.
[Jibei Chamber of Commerce]
[غرفة تجارة جيبي]
So?
لذا؟
He did die of a lightning strike.
لقد مات بسبب ضربة البرق.
What did you find out?
ماذا وجدت؟
Look there.
أنظر هناك.
Obviously, someone else was at the scene.
من الواضح أن شخصًا آخر كان موجودًا في مكان الحادث.
This car was burned so badly,
لقد احترقت هذه السيارة بشدة،
so this bloody handprint
لذا فإن هذه البصمة الدموية
must have appeared after the body was burned.
لا بد أن يكون قد ظهر بعد احتراق الجثة.
And this handprint
وهذه بصمة اليد
is so small,
إنه صغير جدًا
so did a little ghost kill him?
فهل قتله شبح صغير؟
If it really was a little ghost,
لو كان حقا شبحًا صغيرًا،
then the question is
ثم السؤال هو
how did this ghost do it.
كيف فعل هذا الشبح ذلك؟
Based on my estimation,
بناء على تقديري،
the thunder should have gone
كان ينبغي أن يختفي الرعد
through the window.
من خلال النافذة.
Other than the ghost,
بخلاف الشبح،
who could have aimed so accurately?
من كان بإمكانه أن يهدف بهذه الدقة؟
Why is there
لماذا يوجد هناك
a scent in this place?
رائحة في هذا المكان؟
Why it's you guys again?
لماذا أنتم مرة أخرى؟
Didn't we order you to leave?
ألم نأمرك بالخروج؟
Why are you guys involved again?
لماذا أنتم متورطون مرة أخرى؟
Fu Sheng is Lord's Mansion's clerk.
فو شينغ هو كاتب قصر اللورد.
We have the right to investigate.
لدينا الحق في التحقيق.
If you want to hire us,
إذا كنت تريد توظيفنا،
try to pay a high price.
حاول أن تدفع ثمنًا باهظًا.
He did die of a lightning strike.
لقد مات بسبب ضربة البرق.
Anything else?
أي شيء آخر؟
Sorry, I'm not knowledgeable enough.
عذرا، أنا لا أملك المعرفة الكافية.
Good.
جيد.
This is a natural disaster,
هذه كارثة طبيعية
not a man-made one.
ليس من صنع الإنسان.
Say so when you report it to the master.
قل ذلك عندما تبلغه للسيد.
Yes.
نعم.
So hasty?
متسرع جداً؟
There are still doubts about this.
لا تزال هناك شكوك حول هذا الموضوع.
I'm in charge here.
أنا المسؤول هنا.
That's not necessarily true.
هذا ليس صحيحا بالضرورة.
You really call them over?
هل تتصل بهم حقا؟
I just wanted to scare her.
أردت فقط تخويفه.
I haven't had a chance to call them yet.
ولم تتاح لي الفرصة للاتصال بهم بعد.
Miss Tuoba.
السيدة توبا.
For Fu Sheng's sake,
من أجل فو شنغ،
[Jibei Chamber of Commerce] you and your men can go now.
[غرفة تجارة جيبي] أنت ورجالك يمكنكم الذهاب الآن.
That's not
هذا ليس
what the agreement says.
ماذا ينص عليه الاتفاق؟
But you were the first to break it.
ولكنك كنت أول من كسرها.
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد؟
Hua Lei is dead.
هوا لي مات.
Bloody handprints again.
بصمات الأيدي الدموية مرة أخرى.
Let's stop the investigation.
دعونا نوقف التحقيق.
I'm getting scared.
أنا أشعر بالخوف.
This wound is messy.
هذا الجرح فوضوي.
The murderer didn't know how to apply force.
القاتل لم يعرف كيفية استخدام القوة.
The murder weapon is not a good knife
أداة القتل ليست سكينًا جيدًا
and the murderer is not an expert.
والقاتل ليس خبيرا.
But the strange thing is
ولكن الشيء الغريب هو
that Hua Lei didn't show any signs of resistance
أن هوا لي لم يظهر أي علامات مقاومة
when his heart was removed.
عندما تم إزالة قلبه.
Was it done by a ghost?
هل فعل ذلك شبح؟
It's supposed to be a bad martial arts fighter
من المفترض أن يكون مقاتلًا سيئًا في الفنون القتالية
who killed a famous general of the Jibei Chamber of Commerce.
من قتل الجنرال الشهير في غرفة تجارة جيبي؟
Was this done
هل تم هذا؟
by the storyteller's ghost?
من قبل شبح الراوي؟
Yes.
نعم.
Look. There's a ghost's handprint
انظر. هناك بصمة يد شبح
next to his chest.
بجانب صدره.
Little ghosts love to eat people's hearts.
الأشباح الصغيرة تحب أكل قلوب الناس.
They must have dug it out.
لا بد أنهم حفروا ذلك.
Get out of the way.
ابتعد عن الطريق.
Who did this?
من فعل هذا؟
Ma Gang didn't do this.
ما جانج لم يفعل هذا.
It should be Night Owl.
ينبغي أن يكون Night Owl.
Him?
له؟
Hua Lei is strong in fighting.
هوا لي قوي في القتال.
That thief is so cowardly.
هذا اللص جبان جدًا.
When he hears Hua Lei's name, he'll stay away from here,
عندما يسمع اسم هوا لي، سوف يبتعد عن هنا،
so how could he kill Hua Lei?
فكيف يمكنه أن يقتل هوا لي؟
Lord Wen.
اللورد وين.
There must be a conspiracy.
لابد أن تكون هناك مؤامرة.
Chairman Li.
الرئيس لي.
I know you're skeptical,
أعرف أنك متشكك،
but don't be impatient, please.
لكن لا تكن متسرعا، من فضلك.
I will find out the truth for you.
سأكتشف الحقيقة لك.
Someone in the Ma Gang is dead,
لقد مات شخص ما في عصابة ما،
and the same goes for us.
والشيء نفسه ينطبق علينا.
Lord Wen.
اللورد وين.
I need an explanation.
أحتاج إلى توضيح.
Chairman Li,
الرئيس لي،
please think of the big picture.
من فضلك فكر في الصورة الكبيرة.
Lord Wen.
اللورد وين.
The Chamber of Commerce is my big picture.
غرفة التجارة هي صورتي الكبيرة.
My subordinates are seeing if I can be a good leader.
مرؤوسيي يرون إذا كان بإمكاني أن أكون قائدًا جيدًا.
Now that I've said my piece,
الآن بعد أن قلت قطعتي،
I'll take my leave.
سوف آخذ إجازتي.
Mr. Gu.
السيد جو.
Three groups of Ma Gang's swordsmen just walked past.
لقد مرت للتو ثلاث مجموعات من رجال السيوف التابعين لعصابة ما.
Based on their direction,
بناءً على توجيهاتهم،
they seem to be heading for the Jibei Chamber of Commerce.
يبدو أنهم متجهون إلى غرفة تجارة جيبي.
In that case,
في هذه الحالة،
20 teams have gone there at noon.
20 فريقًا ذهبوا إلى هناك عند الظهر.
This time,
هذه المرة،
Ma Gang has basically used
لقد استخدم ما جانج بشكل أساسي
all their living men.
كل رجالهم الأحياء.
Something big is about to happen.
شيء كبير على وشك أن يحدث.
Gu Tian.
قو تيان.
Yingying.
ينغ ينغ.
It's so chaotic out there,
إنه فوضوي للغاية هناك،
but why did you go out?
ولكن لماذا خرجت؟
I heard that the two sides
سمعت أن الجانبين
are about to clash over the recent murder,
على وشك الصدام بسبب جريمة القتل الأخيرة،
and Fu Sheng is the city lord's clerk
وفو شنغ هو كاتب سيد المدينة
in charge of investigating the case.
المكلف بالتحقيق في القضية.
I thought Hearsay-capturing Pavilion
اعتقدت أن جناح التقاط السمع
might be able to help,
قد يكون قادرا على المساعدة،
so I came over.
لذلك جئت.
Then you shouldn't go out either.
إذن لا ينبغي عليك الخروج أيضًا.
It's too dangerous out there.
إنه أمر خطير للغاية هناك.
If something like this happens again,
إذا حدث شيء مثل هذا مرة أخرى،
ask Feng Qianli to let me know,
اطلب من فينج تشيانلي أن يخبرني،
and then I'll come to you.
ومن ثم سآتي إليك.
OK.
نعم.
How's the investigation going?
كيف يسير التحقيق؟
I heard Hua Lei was killed by Night Owl.
سمعت أن هوا لي قُتل على يد Night Owl.
Yes.
نعم.
Night Owl
بومة الليل
is like a mouse
هو مثل الفأر
that goes around making holes.
الذي يدور حول صنع الثقوب.
No one knows where he's hiding.
لا أحد يعرف أين يختبئ.
Leave it to me.
اتركها لي.
There's no one in Xichuan
لا يوجد أحد في شيتشوان
that the Hearsay-capturing Pavilion can't find.
أن جناح التقاط الإشاعات لا يستطيع العثور عليه.
Right.
يمين.
Hulu.
هولو.
Why don't you talk to me when I come?
لماذا لا تتحدث معي عندما أأتي؟
Sis.
أخت.
You two are flirting.
أنتما تغازلان بعضكما البعض.
How can I interrupt?
كيف يمكنني المقاطعة؟
Turn around.
التف حوله.
[Hu's Flatbread Shop]
[متجر هو للخبز المسطح]
Sir.
سيد.
Your pie has no meat filling.
فطيرتك لا تحتوي على حشوة اللحوم.
Do you even complain about the cook when you eat for free?
هل تشتكي من الطباخ عندما تأكل مجانًا؟
Go to Wang.
اذهب إلى وانغ.
He'll fill you up with egg porridge.
سيملأك بعصيدة البيض.
Get lost.
اغرب عن وجهي.
You're so cheap.
أنت رخيص جداً.
Who do you think you are?
من تعتقد نفسك؟
Enjoy.
يتمتع.
[Night Owl appeared in a shabby house on the west side the day before yesterday]
[ظهرت بومة الليل في منزل رث على الجانب الغربي في اليوم السابق للأمس]
I haven't had a hot meal in days
لم أتناول وجبة ساخنة منذ أيام
because I didn't dare to.
لأنني لم أجرؤ على ذلك.
I can't have
لا استطيع الحصول على
too much smoke around here,
هناك الكثير من الدخان هنا،
but today is different,
ولكن اليوم مختلف
because you're here.
لأنك هنا.
You're my favorite apprentice.
أنت المتدرب المفضل لدي.
I don't want you to suffer with me.
لا أريدك أن تعاني معي.
Come on.
تعال.
Have some meat.
خذ بعض اللحوم.
Have you eaten?
هل أكلت؟
Why are you shy in front of your master?
لماذا أنت خجول أمام سيدك؟
Come here.
تعال الى هنا.
Hurry up.
اسرع.
Or
أو
I'll eat you.
سوف آكلك.
Come on.
تعال.
How fresh.
كم هو طازج.
Eat.
يأكل.
Don't fear the pain.
لا تخف من الألم.
You're learning.
أنت تتعلم.
That's how my master taught me.
هكذا علمني سيدي.
If not, I wouldn't be here today.
لو لم يكن كذلك، لما كنت هنا اليوم.
Go on.
إستمر.
This one is good.
هذا جيد.
Go after him.
إذهب خلفه.
He's there.
إنه هناك.
Got him.
حصلت عليه.
Watch out.
احذر.
Are you all right?
هل انت بخير؟
Don't tell anyone I got careless.
لا تخبر أحدا بأنني كنت مهملاً.
OK.
نعم.
Is he playing dead?
هل هو يتظاهر بالموت؟
Did he really pass out?
هل فقد وعيه حقا؟
I've never missed a beat when I'm on the job.
لم أفتقد أي شيء أبدًا عندما كنت في العمل.
[Recover from the Disease] That's right.
[الشفاء من المرض] هذا صحيح.
He's Night Owl.
إنه بومة الليل.
Just a thief.
مجرد لص.
When I'm on the job,
عندما أكون في العمل،
we won't fail.
لن نفشل
I thought I'd be captured by some heroes,
اعتقدت أنني سأقع في قبضة بعض الأبطال،
but I didn't realize
ولكنني لم أدرك ذلك
we were similar.
كنا متشابهين.
Cut the crap.
إقطع الهراء.
How did you kill Hua Lei?
كيف قتلت هوا لي؟
If you dare to hide anything,
إذا تجرأت على إخفاء أي شيء،
I'll ask Fu Sheng
سأسأل فو شنغ
to turn you into this.
لتحويلك إلى هذا.
See?
يرى؟
This knife is best
هذه السكين هي الأفضل
for boning.
لتقطيع العظام.
The girl in Xichuan is so ruthless.
الفتاة في شيتشوان قاسية جدًا.
I know what you're asking,
أنا أعلم ما تسأل عنه،
and I can tell you.
وأستطيع أن أخبرك.
What do you want?
ماذا تريد؟
Where's my apprentice?
أين متدربي؟
Bring him to me,
أحضره إليّ
will you?
سوف تفعل؟
He was hurt too badly,
لقد أصيب بجروح بالغة.
but he's been revived.
ولكنه عاد إلى الحياة.
He's sleeping now.
إنه نائم الآن.
I'm also badly hurt
أنا أيضا مصاب بجروح بالغة
and need to sleep.
وتحتاج إلى النوم.
I'll do it.
سأفعل ذلك.
Prick my finger?
وخز إصبعي؟
It's no fun.
إنه ليس ممتعا.
All right.
حسنًا.
I'll make it interesting for you.
سأجعل الأمر مثيرا للاهتمام بالنسبة لك.
Needle in the toe?
إبرة في إصبع القدم؟
In Yongquan acupoint.
في نقطة الوخز يونغتشيوان.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Why does it itch?
لماذا الحكة؟
I'm improving your blood.
أنا أقوم بتحسين دمك.
I'll say.
سأقول.
Hurry up. We have limited time.
أسرع، لدينا وقت محدود.
The day I got a treasure and came out,
اليوم الذي حصلت فيه على الكنز وخرجت،
I met Hua Lei.
التقيت هوا لي.
He coveted it
لقد طمعَ فيه
and wanted to get his hands on it.
وأراد أن يضع يديه عليه.
So
لذا
you didn't kill him?
لم تقتله؟
Of course not.
بالطبع لا.
He was killed because he was greedy for money.
لقد قُتل لأنه كان جشعًا للمال.
I just cut out his heart.
لقد قطعت قلبه للتو.
Did you do that to his chest?
هل فعلت ذلك بصدره؟
Is it normal to fall off a horse
هل من الطبيعي السقوط من على الحصان
and die?
و يموت؟
What do you think?
ماذا تعتقد؟
More common than death by lightning.
أكثر شيوعا من الموت بسبب البرق.
Watch him.
راقبه.
Where are you going?
إلى أين أنت ذاهب؟
[Like the Rising Sun]
[مثل شروق الشمس]
Even your quail remembers me.
حتى السمان الخاص بك يتذكرني.
So,
لذا،
have you forgotten about me
هل نسيتني؟
when you became Chairman?
متى أصبحت رئيسا؟
How could I?
كيف يمكنني ذلك؟
I'm glad
أنا سعيد
you're here.
انت هنا.
Cut the crap.
إقطع الهراء.
How's the jade plate investigation?
كيف هو التحقيق في لوحة اليشم؟
We're still
نحن لا نزال
working on it.
أعمل عليه.
You mean there's no progress?
هل تقصد أنه لا يوجد تقدم؟
I'm sorry for my incompetence.
أنا آسف لعدم كفاءتي.
Getting a new chairman for the Jibei Chamber of Commerce
تعيين رئيس جديد لغرفة تجارة جيبي
is no harder than killing a quail.
لا يوجد شيء أصعب من قتل السمان.
Li Zhizhuo.
لي تشيتشو.
Are you sure there's nothing else you're not telling me?
هل أنت متأكد من أنه لا يوجد شيء آخر لم تخبرني به؟
I wouldn't dare.
لا أجرؤ على ذلك.
Don't let the Lord down again.
لا تخذل الرب مرة أخرى.
I will do my best to find the jade plate
سأبذل قصارى جهدي للعثور على لوحة اليشم
and deliver it to you.
وتسليمها لك.
Hey...
يا...
My lord!
سيدي!
Once he tells a story about someone, they die.
عندما يحكي قصة عن شخص ما، يموت هذا الشخص.
It's not a coincidence.
إنها ليست مصادفة.
I'm going to talk
انا سأتحدث
Fu Sheng...
فو شنغ...
[Young Heroes: Fu Sheng, Gu Tian]
[الأبطال الشباب: فو شنغ، غو تيان]
and Gu Tian.
وجو تيان.
[The animals in the show are props]
[الحيوانات في العرض هي الدعائم]
[No animals were harmed during the filming]
[لم يتم إيذاء أي حيوان أثناء التصوير]
♪Under the sky, light and shadow go together♪
♪تحت السماء، الضوء والظل يذهبان معًا♪
♪The reflection of prosperity and splendor♪
♪انعكاس الرخاء والروعة♪
♪Hides many secrets♪
♪يخفي العديد من الأسرار♪
♪It's like♪
♪إنه مثل♪
♪Every page of your life♪
♪كل صفحة من حياتك♪
♪It's all about destiny♪
♪الأمر كله يتعلق بالقدر♪
♪The story has tragedy and comedy♪
♪القصة تحتوي على مأساة وكوميديا ​​♪
♪To discover the mystery♪
♪لاكتشاف اللغز♪
♪We go on adventures♪
♪نحن نذهب في مغامرات♪
♪We don't run away or compromise easily♪
♪نحن لا نهرب أو نتنازل بسهولة♪
♪When dawn comes♪
♪عندما يأتي الفجر♪
♪The light shines♪
♪النور يضيء♪
♪We follow the path of discovery♪
♪نحن نتبع طريق الاكتشاف♪
♪To chase and welcome♪
♪ للمطاردة والترحيب ♪
♪Every unknown story♪
♪كل قصة غير معروفة♪
♪We take a trip together♪
♪نحن نقوم برحلة معًا♪
♪With hot blood and original purpose♪
♪مع الدم الساخن والغرض الأصلي♪
♪We seize the day and live it to the fullest♪
♪نحن نستغل اليوم ونعيشه على أكمل وجه♪
♪Leave a mark on our journey♪
♪اترك علامة في رحلتنا♪
♪Scatter the darkness with our hearts♪
♪نبدد الظلام بقلوبنا♪
♪Aspire to make a difference♪
♪أطمح إلى إحداث فرق♪
♪To discover the mystery♪
♪لاكتشاف اللغز♪
♪We go on adventures♪
♪نحن نذهب في مغامرات♪
♪We don't run away or compromise easily♪
♪نحن لا نهرب أو نتنازل بسهولة♪
♪When dawn comes♪
♪عندما يأتي الفجر♪
♪The light shines♪
♪النور يضيء♪
♪We follow the path of discovery♪
♪نحن نتبع طريق الاكتشاف♪
♪To chase and welcome♪
♪ للمطاردة والترحيب ♪
♪Every unknown story♪
♪كل قصة غير معروفة♪
♪We take a trip together♪
♪نحن نقوم برحلة معًا♪
♪With hot blood and original purpose♪
♪مع الدم الساخن والغرض الأصلي♪
♪We seize the day and live it to the fullest♪
♪نحن نستغل اليوم ونعيشه على أكمل وجه♪
♪Leave a mark on our journey♪
♪اترك علامة في رحلتنا♪
♪Scatter the darkness with our hearts♪
♪نبدد الظلام بقلوبنا♪
♪Aspire to make a difference♪
♪أطمح إلى إحداث فرق♪
♪Make a difference♪
♪أحدث فرقًا♪
♪We take a trip together♪
♪نحن نقوم برحلة معًا♪
♪Through hardships♪
♪من خلال الصعوبات♪
♪We will find the glory♪
♪سوف نجد المجد♪
♪Aspire to make a difference♪
♪أطمح إلى إحداث فرق♪